https://www.brotherstrucks.com/privacy.asp

Attention: COVID-19 Update - Our customer service and showroom are OPEN. Package shipments are currently taking 2-3 days to process, and UPS/USPS are also experiencing extended delivery times. As of 10/6/2020, most orders are being delivered within 7-10 days of the order date. We appreciate your business and apologize for the inconvenience. Read more.
TRUCK SHOWS
|
DIY ARTICLES
|
BLOG
|
|
1-800-977-2767
|
View Cart (0)
DEPARTMENTS
1947-1955.1
NEW ITEMS
Interior
Dash Components
Dash Repair Panels
Instrument Bezels
Gauges
Our Commitment to Privacy
Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our Website or use the BROTHERS Trucks Mobile Application you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Website.
1. Personal Information You Choose to Provide
Credit Card Information If you choose to purchase products or services from us or our partners, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:
Name
Mailing address
Email address
Credit card number
Home and business phone number
Other personal information (i.e. mother's maiden name)
Email Information
In addition to providing the foregoing information to our partners, if you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.
2. Website and Mobile App Use Information
Similar to other commercial Websites, our Website and Mobile App utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and web server logs to collect information about how our Website and Mobile App are being used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Website, and the Websites visited just before and just after our Website. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website,
new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers' personal information. As a customer, you will be given the opportunity, at least once annually, to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers.
What Are Cookies?
Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Website. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Website by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.
How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?
We use Website browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Website users' browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our Website and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Website to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers.
Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Website as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Website and evaluate our Website's visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally identifying information about you although they do permit us to send focused online banner advertisements or other such responses to you.
We utilize the help of third-party ad platforms, including Google, in order to tailor ads specifically to you as you browse the web. Our ads may appear on other websites, and are based on past visits that you may have made to our website in order to provide ads that you will like. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies at any time by visiting Google's Ad Settings.
Sharing Information with Affiliates
From time to time you may notice offers from outside companies advertised on our Website. We take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford privacy protections to their customers. However, we cannot make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies.
Sharing Information with Strategic Partners
We may enter into strategic marketing alliances or partnerships with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with strategic marketing alliances or partnerships, we will retain all ownership rights to the information, and we will not share information regarding your social security number or other personal financial data.
Notice of New Services and Changes
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our client, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking on a response box when you receive such an offer or by sending us an email request at "Webmaster@BrothersTrucks.com".
How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?
When you send confidential personal credit card information to us on our Website, a secure server software which we have licensed encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. The information is scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches our Website.
Other email that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as Social Security or account numbers to us through an unsecured email.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
Information Security. We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.
Evaluation of Information Protection Practices. Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our information.
Employee Access, Training and Expectations. Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions.
How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing "Webmaster@BrothersTrucks.com".
Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?
We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Website traffic patterns and related Website information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.
What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
What About Other Websites Linked to Our Website?
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Websites linked to or from our Website nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Website.
Company Information
Contact Us
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Site Map
Color Samples
My Account
View Cart
follow us on...
